export const PlacementData = [
  {
    question: '2+5 =',
    options: [25, 7, 6],
    correctoption: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "The synonym of 'evil' is",
    options: ['Good', 'Wicked', 'Generous'],
    correctoption: 'Wicked',
  },
  {
    question: 'The 22nd alphabet is',
    options: ['v', 't', 'w'],
    correctoption: 'v',
  },
  {
    question: 'One of the five senses in human is',
    options: ['Smile', 'Fight', 'Sight'],
    correctoption: 'Sight',
  },
  {
    question: '67.42 - 28.58',
    options: [38.57, 38.84, 38.94],
    correctoption: 38.84,
  },
  {
    question: 'The capital letter of ‘g’ is',
    options: ['B', 'E', 'G'],
    correctoption: 'G',
  },
  {
    question: 'Doctor’s job is to',
    options: ['Kill a patient', 'Eat a patient', 'Cure patient'],
    correctoption: 'Cure patient',
  },
  {
    question: 'The capital city of Indonesia is',
    options: ['Jakarta', 'Maluku', 'Medan'],
    correctoption: 'Jakarta',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many legs does a cat have?',
    options: [4, 5, 6],
    correctoption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      'Initially, I have five apples. My friend stole one piece, and my brother ate one. How many apples do I have now?',
    options: [1, 2, 3],
    correctoption: 3,
  },
];
